[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Canadian comedy troupe started out in 1984 and included actor Dave Foley.", "correct_answer": "Kids in the Hall", "incorrect_answers": ["New kids on the Block", "Big kids in the Hood", "Kids in the Attic"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The exchange of letters between these two people was published in 1933 under the title Why War?.", "correct_answer": "Einstein and Freud", "incorrect_answers": ["Hitler and Mussolini", "Stalin and Lenin", "Franklin and Eleanor Roosevelt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Fleur de sel?", "correct_answer": "Natural sea salt", "incorrect_answers": ["A species of seaweed that live only in sea water with very high salinity", "A plant that contains the highest amount of sodium chloride of all plants", "A type of salty French biscuits"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Warm weather brings high pressure systems.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Warner Brothers approached many directors before signing William Friedkin to direct The Exorcist. Which of these directors was NOT approached?", "correct_answer": "John Schlesinger", "incorrect_answers": ["Peter Bogdanovich", "Stanley Kubrick", "Mike Nichols"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In order to achieve the widest possible field of view, these animals have their two eyes positioned on opposite sides of their heads.", "correct_answer": "Prey animals", "incorrect_answers": ["Predatory animals", "Underwater animals", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the capital of Greece?", "correct_answer": "Athens", "incorrect_answers": ["Ankara", "Sofia", "Thessaloniki"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the predominant color in Amazon Parrots plumage?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "White", "Blue"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is the Red Fox a protected species in most parts of the world?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This can be viewed as a generalization of the Pythagorean Theorem.", "correct_answer": "Law of Cosines", "incorrect_answers": ["Law of  Willens", "Law of Cotangents", "Law of Verseed Sines"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Ethiopias capital is Addis Ababa.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed King Philip II in the 2004 movie Alexander?", "correct_answer": "Val Kilmer", "incorrect_answers": ["Anthony Hopkins", "Colin Farrell", "Heath Ledger"]}]